https://www.pregnancycareinfo.org/p/privacy-policy.html

-->
air pollutionAvoid During PregnancyBaby Kicking During Pregnancybaby movingBabyStoresbeauty tips during pregnancyBodily ChangescoronaCoronaviruscovid 19CrampsDentist During PregnancyDepression in Pregnancydeveloping babyExerciseFaintnessFetal Developmentfetal growthFetal WeightFirst Signs Of PregnancyFirst Trimester of PregnancyGestational DiabetesGrowth charthave sexhealth care providerHealthy BabyHealthy Eating While PregnantHow Poor Sleep During PregnancyIndigestionMaternitystoresMedicationsmedicineMiscarriageNauseaovulatePiercing During the PregnancyPregnancy Do’s and Don’tspregnancy informationpregnancyinformationPrenatal care checkupsRhRH Negative Blood Type and PregnancyRhoGAMSafe Hair Removal
During PregnancySafe Sex Positions During PregnancyShavingsicknessSkin Care TipsSleepingSleeping Positions During PregnancysmokeSpider Veins During PregnancyStages Of PregnancyThe Baby MovementsThe Diabetes Mellitus and PregnancyTimeline of Baby MovementTreatment for a MiscarriagetwinsUrinary ProblemsVascular spidersVitamin
main menu
Pages
Type your search keyword
edit-post
Privacy policy
GOGO
10 September 2018
Privacy policy for I am Pregnant team blog
If you need any further information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by
Page Contact Us -
In the I am Pregnant team blog,
The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information it receives and collects
Blog I am Pregnant team and how to use it. Log Files Like so many web sites, the blog uses the I am Pregnant team log files. The information inside the log files includes: Internet protocol, IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), date / time rings, sources of traffic / exit pages, number of clicks to analyze trends and manage site and control user on the go Site, and demographic information collection. IP addresses, and other such information is not associated with any information to identify you. Google search box: The search box on this website ("search box") is provided by Google ("Google"). You acknowledge and agree to the Google Privacy Policy (located at http://www.google.com/privacy.html)
By using the "Search Box" and using the "Search Box" Google grants approval to use your personal data in accordance with the Privacy Policy. Mailing List: By registering in the I am Pregnant mailing list, the privacy of your address will remain respected and will not be published. Cookies and Web Beacons: The I am Pregnant Team Blog uses cookies to store information about visitors' settings, and specific user information is logged when entering or visiting a page. The content of a Web page is customized based on browser type of visitors or other information when the visitor sends information via the browser. Cookies DoubleClick DoubleClick Share - Google as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. - Use Google DART Cookie to serve ads to users based on visiting websites and other web sites. - Users may choose not to use DART cookies by visiting the Google Content and Privacy Network at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Some advertising partners may use cookies, files on our site, and our advertising partners include Google Adsense . These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display ads and links that appear in the I am Pregnant team blog and are sent directly to browsers. It automatically gets an IP address when this happens. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or network counters) can also be used by third parties such as ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their ads and / or to personalize the content of the ad you see. The I am Pregnant Team Blog can not access / control these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult all the privacy policies of these third party ad servers for more detailed information about their practices as well as for instructions on how to get out of some practices. The privacy policy of the I am Pregnant Team Code does not apply to them, and we can not monitor their activities, Internet. If you want to disable cookies, you can do so through your browser options. For more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found on the websites of browsers
What to avoid during pregnancy?
What is depression during pregnancy ?
